[theme music playing]
Hi, I'm Cory, Cory Carson.
-[laughs]
-Hey, kiddo.
♪ Go! Go! ♪
Cory!
[all cheering]
-Chrissy!
-♪ Go! Go! ♪
Whee!
-Come back here.
-♪ Go! Go! ♪
[cheering]
-[train whistle blowing]
♪ Cory Carson ♪
[car horn honks]
[Cory] "Show & Tell."
-Gather round, kids.
-[kid] Yes!
-It's time for show-and-tell.
-[all cheering]
Check out what I brought
for show-and-tell.
-Whoa!
-[Cory] It's a self-portrait.
It looks just like you!
You're gonna have
the best show-and-tell ever!
[both vocalizing]
For my show-and-tell, I brought in a piece
from my broken car parts collection.
It's a hood from a limousine
that got hit by a meteorite!
[all oohing]
And I still have the meteorite.
[all] Wow!
-[Cory] What?
-Nice!
Oh, my gosh, it's so crazy.
What planet is it from?
In 12 years of teaching
in three different school districts,
never have I seen
such an amazing show-and-tell.
[all cheering]
[laughs] Wow, I wouldn't want to go next.
Cory, are you ready to go next?
Uh... [grunts]
I left my show-and-tell at home.
But it's super cool.
Oh, good. Then we can't wait
to see your super cool show-and-tell
first thing tomorrow morning.
Mmm.
[Cory] No. No.
No! [groans]
[Chrissy] No, no, no!
Cory, is everything okay in here?
No. Halle had
the best show-and-tell of all time today,
and it's my turn tomorrow morning.
Oh, come on,
it couldn't have been that good.
What did Halle bring?
A glowing meteorite from outer space.
Whoa! Did you get a picture of that or--?
-Papa!
-[laughs]
Don't worry, Cory,
I'll help you find something.
Let's see.
Hey! How about the first toy
Mama and I ever got you?
The Tubby Tugboats!
Yeah! We bought those for you
when you just a "widdle" baby car.
Yeah. I lost those a long time ago.
Found 'em.
Uh, I can't take these to show-and-tell.
They're for babies!
Aw, but you used to love
the Tubby Tugboats.
Mm, I don't know.
[toy] I love you!
[Chrissy]
Hee hee hee hee!
[groans]
Well, if Tubby Tugboats won't work,
we'll find something else.
-Like what?
-Like...
a buried treasure!
Really? Where, Papa, where?
Stay back, pal.
[grunting]
Cool!
When I was your age, I went
on a fishing trip to Bumperstone.
I ended up stranded out in the wild
for five whole days!
Oh, my gosh!
I was sure I was a goner.
That is, until I made the discovery
that saved my life.
[gasps] Oh, my g--
Wait a second,
it's just an old cup of pudding.
Not just any old cup of pudding.
The very cup of pudding I ate from
to survive the wilds of Bumperstone!
What am I supposed to do with it?
Take it to school!
A crusty old pudding cup? How is that
supposed to be cooler than a meteorite?
Oh, well, I never said it was
cooler than a meteorite.
[groans]
Don't worry,
we'll figure this out together.
[sighs] Okay, Papa.
That's the spirit!
Now how about, uh...
-Cactus?
-No.
-Honkin' Henry?
-No!
-Honkin' Henry with sunglasses?
-Beans?
-Nope.
-Unicar horn?
-No.
-Bouncy balls?
-No!
Ahh! This isn't working!
Oh. Hmm. Well, what's wrong, Cory?
None of this stuff is cool enough!
Oh, uh, I was just trying to help.
I never even asked for your help!
Oh, well, I'm sorry.
[sighs] I'll do it myself.
Uhhh...
Grrrr!
Hey Cory. Did you and Papa
find something for show-and-tell?
No. Nothing we have
is cooler than a meteorite.
Hmm.
You know, Cory,
show-and-tell isn't a competition.
Don't worry about bringing something cool.
Just find something you really love
and share that with the class.
Huh.
-[Chrissy] Whee! [laughs]
-Huh?
Go, Papa, faster, faster, faster!
Whee, Papa. Whee, Papa. Whee, Papa!
[school bell rings]
Um...
Do you have your lunch?
Yeah.
Okay, then.
Have a good day.
Uh, Papa!
Wait.
What's up, Cory?
Well, I was just thinking...
would you maybe like to come
and watch show-and-tell today?
Well, sure, Cory.
If you want me to.
Yeah, yeah. Follow me.
Okay, class, gather round
for show-and-tell.
Cory, take it away.
Today, for my show-and-tell, I wanted
to bring in something extra-special.
[all gasping]
It wasn't an easy decision,
but I wanted
to choose something I really love.
My papa!
[all] Huh?
-Huh?
-Come on, Papa!
He's an expert popcorn maker
and a champion bumper bowler.
My Papa even braved
the wilds of Bumperstone,
living on nothing
but a single cup of pudding.
[all] Whoa!
Ehh. It was nothin', really.
Not to mention,
he's the best cartoonist in town.
Who wants to get their picture drawn?
-[all] Me! Me! Me!
-Best show-and-tell ever!
Okay, one at a time.
[all clamoring]
[theme music playing]